Samuel Mason

10000 Gate Pkwy N Apt 325, Jacksonville, Florida 32246 • (678) 549-2086 • samuelmason5@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Experienced Support Analyst with a history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in C#, Test Driven Development, SOLID design patterns, and Microsoft SQL Server. Strong information technology professional with a B.S focused in Information Technology from Georgia Southern University. Ready to bring one year of software development experience to a challenging new role as a software developer.

Work History

Application Support Analyst, 03/2017 to 11/2018

System Innovators Inc - Jacksonville, Florida

- Develop C# .Net application for support team to use to assist in everyday tasks to troubleshoot product.
- Create and maintain documentation for developed application for use by end users.
- Collaborate with support team and clients to identify and resolve issues related to the product.
- Schedule and attend remote meetings with end users and to implement and maintain product.
- Communicate with end users the resolution to resolve issues experienced with product.
- Ensure all components of the product perform properly in client environments.
- Build knowledge base documentation to help end users in common troubleshooting situations.

Database Administrator Intern, 05/2016 to 08/2016

CSX Technology - Jacksonville, Florida

Database Services Team

- Learned how to perform responsibilities of a database administrator of DB2 databases.
- Implemented changes to databases requested by application developers.
- Assisted with duplicate database elimination project.

Jacksonville Urban League Team

- Designed and developed website platform for the Jacksonville Urban League.
- Designed and implemented a MySQL database to support the data for the website platform.
- Gathered requirements from business partners in person and remotely.
- Worked with a team to implement features requested by the customer.

Desktop Support Student Technician, 09/2014 to 12/2016

Georgia Southern University - Statesboro, Georgia

- Worked with a team to troubleshoot and resolve hardware and software issues with computer systems.
- Solved issues affecting end users across multiple departments in a large enterprise environment.
- Received work requests through ticketing platform to establish and prioritize workflow.
- Provided support for end users to understand and resolve computer, printer, and networking issues.
- Utilized SQL to create and maintain inventory database to help prepare for end of year device refresh.

Skills

- C# .Net development
- JavaScript
- Angular
- SQL

- Test Driven Development
- SOLID Design Patterns
- Technical Documentation
- Application Support

Education

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology, 2016 **Georgia Southern University** - Statesboro, Georgia